<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Mord Update]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am Mord. I serve my lord Kord with my greatsword. Misspeak I do.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 13:16:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://mord.jostylr.com/rssupdate.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><author><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></author><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2014 13:16:43 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[2014 James Taylor]]></copyright><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><managingEditor><![CDATA[Janord Drom]]></managingEditor><webMaster><![CDATA[James Taylor]]></webMaster><ttl>1440</ttl><category><![CDATA[fantasy]]></category><item><title><![CDATA[BaffledMint]]></title><description><![CDATA[The plans we will make. Fiola and Starg are here at the feast with me, drinking and carrying on. We are all here. So is my mother, radiant now that she has hope and now that the Sword of Drok lies in her son's hands.

For tonight, we celebrate the end of the plague of BaffledMint. What lies next, only time will tell. I must rescue my father and there is a whole continent to claim and tame. And there is one sassy warmage to take as my own. But first, let me tell you of our great deeds.

We had escaped the maze and killed the weak guards in front of BaffledMint's throne room. We entered with gusto. The demon looked at us and snorted.

"Who dares enter my chambers?!"

I stepped forward, "I am Mord. I server my lord Kord with this greatsword. We demand that you leave our word alone."

Barrel rolled his eyes. BaffledMint chortled. "Ah. Of course. Well, I hope you put up a good fight. Today has been a very boring day so far."

And so began a long battle. Goat men descended on us as a wall of blades blocked our access to the throne. BaffledMint glared at Barrel who suddenly vanished. I beseeched Kord to bring him back and which he did with a plop. BaffledMint looked annoyed and glared at me.

One of the snake ladies in the room disappeared. ThrowDown threw a fireball into the middle of the room, incinerating most of the goat-men.

Pitter charged through the blades, being sliced along the way in his attempt to get at our enemies. I prepared to do the same but then BaffledMint turned his attention to me. He used his powers to send me away. I tried to reflect his attempt back at him, but my reflection was reflected back. A great purple stream was setup between BaffledMint. I gritted my teeth, holding on as long as I could, but in the end, I was swept away to another place, a pocket maze. A vile, disgusting maze.

Enraged at being separated from the battle, I cried out, "Kord, grant me passaged out of this accursed maze and bring me face to face with the coward BaffledMint." The maze dissolved and as I swung my sword into nothingness, it connected with the great, towering form of BaffledMint.

The Sword of Drok pulsed with joy. A demon-god to kill, I heard it sing. BaffledMint sneered and swiped at me with his great jagged flaming spear. We exchanged blows while Pitter clubbed him from the other side.

Blow for blow, the contest of strength and steel went on. Later I learned that the snake ladies had summoned a small army to attack which ThrowDown and Barrel fought off. They looked close to death when I found them.

But as I was nearing my own end, I finally saw a perfect opening. Pitter had just clubbed BaffledMint at the neck, and in that moment of distraction, I thrust the Sword of Drok deep into BaffledMint's dark heart. He glared at me, laughed, and disappeared.

I cursed him, the coward. The fighting ceased as his minions vanished. The tower started to shake. And his voice rang out. "Well, well. You do fight well. Since I enjoyed our little fun today, I shall grant you your desire. I will stop by mining operations on your world, for now. But if I ever see you here again, I will kill you. Now, begone!"

Pitter helped me over to the others, who were sprawled out on the floor, nearly dead, but conscious. We joined hands as I transported all of us back to our world, back to the elven lands.

We rested for a few days as feast preparations were made. I went and got Fiola and Starg for the festival. After much feasting and drinking, plans were discussed for the future. My eyes wandered over to Fiola who looked back at me with a mischievous grin. I swore to get my father back and to reestablish our colony. ISear agreed that those lands to the south would be ours as far as the giants were concerned. ThrowDown and Barrel decided to go demon-hunting on the far continent while Pitter was to stay and help ISear organize their people for the journey back.

Our little band of heroes was at an end, but our journeys were just beginning.

Mords of Wisdom: The end is but the beginning.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/baffledmint..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/baffledmint..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Maze]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am annoyed. We are lost in some sick maze full of goatmen.

So we woke up and left the Great Hall, to return to the Abyss. We had decided the safest course of action was to teleport to the distant tower. We want to conserve our strength for the demon lord Baffled Mint.

I teleported all of us to wall by the keep. We could see a small army of minotaurs on the walkways across a moat of molten lava. They seemed to be marching out. The courtyard of the keep seemed empty. We flew over to the tallest tower and tried to get in.

It took much magical and physical bashing, but we eventually made it inside. And then we hit this awful maze.

The others are busy drawing diagrams and considering where we have been. I have found it all very confusing. Every room is connected to other rooms in ways that make no sense.

In a room with a fountain, we had walked in a circle by going straight through several rooms. I took a shot with my sling to see if it would come back, but it seemed to fall short.

Barrel grinned, took aim with his bow, and shot into the other room. I stepped back, smiling, "Ranger needs healing." Barrel looked puzzled and then gasped in shock as his arrow dug deep into his backside. Laughing, I sauntered over and healed him.

Moving on, we encountered several goat demons. Barrel was energized at killing them, but I found the contest far too easy. We took turns doing the slaying.

And now we have been searching for hours. There is a promising stairway ahead. Perhaps that will lead up this accursed tower.

Mords of Wisdom: When power bends back on itself, it is best to be weak.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/a-maze..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/a-maze..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Braving the Nothing]]></title><description><![CDATA[It was the stuff of legends. The gate about to open. A party of battle-scarred heroes ready to take on an army of demons. Weapons of power. Lightning crackling.

I gripped the Sword of Drok and yelled into the void. It was cold and swirling. Then hot and streaming. Dark and light, heat and cold, life and death, they were all mixing and singing in this corridor. And suddenly, it stopped.

I blinked. It was dark. So very dark. But in the vast distances, I could see a variety of blue and red portals scattered around in the distance. Creatures seemed to be walking into the blue and coming out of the red. I looked back just as Pitter was falling through. I stepped aside, but he was too big and we both ended up on the ground. Soon, ThrowDown and Barrel were sprawled across. LowShow scampered along with Barrel.

And then the gate shut down. All was black. I signalled to fly up.

As we did so, we could see flames shooting up from the planes, illuminating a massive round area with portals and tunnels ringing the sides. As we flew up, we could see that there was a vast maze surrounding our entrance plain.

We came to rest on one of the walls and took a look around. It seemed that there were a great many cries and shrieks from the maze. We could see many dark shapes flying above the maze. In the distance, we could see a large fortress. We assume that is Baffled Mint's place.

As we pondered what to do, a great shriek erupted. A flying serpent had dived and latched onto Pitter. I was next to him and swung the Sword of Drok at the creature just as ThrowDown hurled a massive green ball of light at it. The creature's scaly back started to melt away just as my sword plunged deep into the opening, killing the creature instantly.

Pitter collapsed under the pain and weight of the beast. After shoving the beast off the wall, we decided to retire for the night while I tend to Pitter's wounds. I summoned the Great Hall of Kord and we all entered into it, for a good night of feasting, drinking, and sleeping.

Mords of Wisdom: Always carry a feast in your pocket.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/braving-the-nothing..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/braving-the-nothing..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dust to Life]]></title><description><![CDATA[I sat there stunned for awhile, staring at my uncle's body and the pulsating gate. There was not long left before the gate would be open again. The battles of the hills seemed to be ending, the noises fading, the showers of rocks no more. The others looked to me.

I grimaced, grabbed the sword, cut my hand, and swore: "By Kord, I shall see these deeds through." I went over to Arry's backpack and starting searching. And there I found packs of diamond dust. Enough to raise us all.

With renewed spirit, I set out to resurrect my uncle. It took a few minutes, but the power of Kord was soon flowing through me and in to Arry, revitalizing him. He awoke with a start.

"Arry, glad you could join us. How was death?"

He stared at me, blinked, smiled, and then said, "Relaxing. I seemed to be fighting hordes of crazy librarians as I strove to defend a tower of books. What a strange afterlife. Let's see, I suppose you need me to shut down the gate?"

I nodded. Only Arry knew enough to permanently disable the gate. And I needed to go hunt down a demon lord.

ISear will stay with Arry while they shut the gate down. The rest of us are preparing to jump into the unknown.

Mords of Wisdom: Always pack some diamond dust.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/dust-to-life..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/dust-to-life..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Snake Ladies]]></title><description><![CDATA[I wish I could say that none of us died.

It was perhaps the most disorganized ambush we have ever done.

Most of the demons guarding the portal were dispatched to investigate the rampaging hills. From what we could tell, a single snake lady demon remained.

The light of the portal to another realm was calling with lightning hailing down randomly around the gate. I knew that our best chance would be to try to block the portal before engaging with the enemy.

So I decided to sneak down to the portal. Pitter went with me as we both could cover the ground very quickly.

Throwdown, ISear, and Arry followed us at a healthy distance while Barrel and his wolf covered us from on high.

As it turns out, Barrel was not far enough away.

As Pitter and I came down, the snake lady suddenly vanished. I broke out into a run, getting into just the right distance to beseech Kord to close the portal.

I could feel the energies whip back at me, my body electrifying as the lightning strode down towards me only to be deflected by the might of Kord. The portal went from blue to red.

At that moment, I smelled an awful stench and heard a plop. Massive horn-rimmed toads suddenly surrounded me, just as Pitter caught up to me. Glancing back, I could see that Barrel was surrounded by two snake ladies as well as another horde of toad creatures. Our middle group was struggling with two towering bear-like creatures.

Focusing on the toad demons in front of me, Pitter and I dispatched them rather quickly. Their bodies decayed into nauseating pools of slime. As I wiped off my sword and began to take steps to help the others, a snake lady popped in front of me. She had six arms with six swords, a strong whipping tail, and hair of snakes. One of her swords seemed to shine a dark brilliance in the light.

She attacked in a flurry of blows, but Pitter and I blocked and dodged her attacks. Pitter counterattacked, staggering her a bit. I then let loose my own flurry of blows. I could see the pain of death in her eyes as I swung my blade for one final killing blow. She raised her shiniest sword to block my blow, my sword crashed into it and shattered. With anguished rage, I continued past her defenses and plunged the jagged remains of my sword into her throat. She staggered back, her mouth open in a silent gasp, and then a thousand snakes flew out as her body crumpled inwards, her remains gone.

I looked down at my mother's broken sword. Curse these demons, I thought. Pitter patted me on the back and then swung violently at a bear-like creature that had crept up on us. A familiar gassy shape floated by us; it seemed to be Throwdown. He never was very good in a one-on-one fight. I looked up the path. ISear and Arry had dispatched the other bear-like creature and moved into help Barrel.

Pitter seemed to have the bear-like creature under control. I slipped away and ran up the path. As I ran, Barrel finished the last of the toad creatures, leaving just a single snake lady. I learned later that the second snake lady attacking Barrel had been an illusion. Barrel had managed to get away from the fight and was bringing his bow to bear. And then I saw it. The snake lady grabbed Arry with her tail and then sliced him into pieces. She flung his mangled corpse down towards me.

His sword, the Sword of Drok, went spinning off the cliffside. I could feel power calling out to me. I reached out my hand and commanded the sword to come to me. And it flew into my hands, as I leaped over Arry's body and unleashed a furious hail of blows on the snake lady. "For the glory of Kord and the vengeance of my blood, you shall be cast down." And so it was that the Sword of Drok slew its first demon in over a thousand years. It glowed with cold, silver light, tinged with red as I plunged the sword into the demon's heart and flung the writhing body over my head and into the ravine where it exploded in a shower of snakes. As the blood soaked into the sword, I could see clearly the ways of snake demons.

Taking a deep breath, I looked around. All was quiet. Arry was dead. Barrel was barely breathing. ThrowDown wafted down from above and took solid form again.

I looked at him. "Glad you got our back," I said with disdain dripping in my words as my gaze fell upon the fallen body of my uncle. If I only had some diamond dust...

Mords of Wisdom: Be prepared for an ambush while ambushing.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/snake-ladies..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/snake-ladies..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Earth Pounders]]></title><description><![CDATA[Barrel found some dull-witted mining demons. Rather red, blobby creatures with little wings and very large eyes. We tried to get some information out of them, but we are really bad about not killing demons. They died spectacularly though; their bodies went pop and then they oozed into the ground. LowShow was sniffing at the ooze and when Barrel tried to shoo her away from it, he slipped and got rather covered in the sticky stuff. So with a wave of the hand, I washed him clean with Kord's spit. He grimaced.

We decided to just fly roundabout to the light. At the crest of a mountain we could see that there was a shining portal and that materials were being carried up and into the portal. Around the gate, there seemed to be a decent sized group of demons hanging out.

"We could always storm them," I suggested. This was not met with much approval, as I had suspected. "Or we could distract them and I could try to seal the gate." This seemed to meet with more approval.

ThrowDown had an idea. "The earth around here cries out in agony. It wants to rip these demons apart. So I think I shall oblige it. Give me some time and I can create havoc in their ranks."

So now we wait. He seems to be almost done. So far, I see several extremely large hills forming, hills with some pretty massive arms. They are starting to pace. I have never seen hills pacing before. It makes me dizzy.

And now he comes back: "They are ready. This army of elementals will march down into the valley and destroy the defilers."

The hills are moving, not a sound to be heard. Now we must prepare. I can already hear the death cries of demons.

Mords of Wisdom: Control the terrain to win a battle.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/earth-pounders..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/earth-pounders..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sword of Drok]]></title><description><![CDATA[We made it to the mountains. ISear is alternating between rage and tears. His home has been utterly destroyed, the forests leveled, the ground and mountains being ripped open in some sort of mining operation. And in this darkness, there is a light shooting into the heavens, a cracking, frantic light.

Barrel is doing some scouting, ThrowDown is pacing, and Pitter is digging a trough for ISear's tears.

Arry motions to me into the shadows.

"Mord, I need to tell you about this sword. Do you remember the story of Drok?"

"Drok, yes, the mighty companion of Kord and the founder of Kord's temple. A brute of a man, I have been told. Until the day he disappeared, no one save Kord could best him in feats of athleticism. I always felt a kinship to him."

"Well, Mord, there is a good reason for that feeling. Your mother forbade me to speak of it to you, but events have demanded otherwise and she agrees now. Drok would have been amazing enough if what you say was all. But he was also a master smith and a clever wizard. Those were the days of legendary people. He forged this sword, his sword, and put in all his knowledge, experience, and wisdom into making it. It hums with goodness, singing happily as it fells those of evil kind, made of a unique blend of silver and cold iron. Hold it, do you hear its song?"

I held it and felt a warmth go up my arm, a closeness to the divine that I have only felt when I am wrapped in the power of Kord. It sang to me of demons in close proximity. As I swung it, a calm rage of joy ripped into me. I gave it back to Arry, reluctantly.

"Thank you Mord. I need to study it a bit more, to make sure it has not been cursed. Fortunately, the magic of the orcs is generally pretty poor. You should have the sword soon Mord. For this sword is your birthright. Many years ago, before the temple at New Ardlord or the colony, I pieced together the legends and writings that led your mother and me to this sword. Well, led me to tell your mother where to go. She did the leg work, you know. I was never much good in a fight. And those were some pretty brutal fights, ancient crypts buried underneath a jungle of ferocious monsters.

"But why could we do this?  You see, Mord, my sister and I were the last descendants of Drok. Now you will be once we are gone. This sword had been lost for centuries, waiting for the time to reappear and do great deeds. It was the finding of this sword that prompted the temple elders to approve the sect of Drok to go to New Ardlord. And it was its divine inspiration that led us to further explore into the colony upon these shores. This sword was a symbol of hope and inspiration.

"It was your mother who was a rising star in the temple. She and this sword, leading and battling to prominence. She became arrogant. Yes, Mord, she did. She led us to these shores before we were ready. The first tribe we met was your father's. They were ready to annihilate us. But she did battle with that whole tribe. Just her, in fact. And she beat them all, without killing a single one. That feat earned her respect amongst them all. She told them of the power of Kord, of his mercy, and of his joy of athletic combat. And so it was that they swore upon the sword to serve Kord.

"But the entire plain was filled with orcs and they were not as compliant. We stood our ground for years, but in the end, it was doomed to fail. Our numbers started to dwindle. We had no support from home. And then, the great orc alliance was formed; we had thousands of orcs coming at us. Your father and his best orcs stayed behind to defend us in our retreat. Your mother gave him this sword and and a glass sphere to transport him back to her when the time came. But he never came back. The sword was lost. Your mother could find no trace of him. The temple elders were most displeased, she fell out of favor, and the whispers of your father's presumed betrayal entered her heart. This is why she has lost so much of her vibrancy. But now, now, we have the sword back and your father's fate is known. There was no betrayal, but rather dark magic. I have told my sister of all of this and I can sense the spark coming back. I hope it is not too late. But for now, we must deal with the situation here. I fear that what we have seen confirms that there is an open portal to a demon's plane, presumably that beast BaffledMint. We must close it for good."

He talks and talks, but I not listen. Pretty sword, me thinks.

Mords of Wisdom: Arrogance drives one to rise high and fall low.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/sword-of-drok..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/sword-of-drok..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Darkening Flight]]></title><description><![CDATA[Arry and I flew towards the party. They had scattered, but I could sense they were gathering again. As we flew, I could see the ground below was desolate. In front of us, towards the mountains, the darkness seemed to swallow reality itself.

Cold and windy, this was not the plains I remembered. Arry looked grim.

When we met with the others, they reported that far and wide over the plains, it was all the same. Just burned out ruins, devastated grounds, the occasional pile of bones. No life was left.

As we munched on some food, I felt a sadness that the blood of the orcs that took my father will never be on my hands.

To the ever darkening mountains we go.

Mords of Wisdom: Vengeance reveals itself in that the act itself is sweet while the result is bitter.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/darkening-flight..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/darkening-flight..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ruins of a Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is hard. I am flying fast and trying to talk this out. Not easy. But here it goes.

We teleported to the site of the old colony, or rather, on the hill overlooking it. My aim was a bit rusty and Barrel ended up in a tree--he seemed happy about that and it took awhile for him to come down. Pitter was shaking the tree for awhile and then broke it in half--weak trees. Throwdown looked on in exasperation. Arry was gauging the air and ISear just stood tall. Me, well, I ran.

I ran down to the old town, the town I knew and loved. I could not contain myself. I am rather ashamed at how it just overcame me like that. Caution thrown to the wind, I went screaming down. I could almost hear the battle, see the fires, the orc grunts and the steel upon steel. My blood ran hot while my heart grew cold.

My sword pulsed in my hands, my throat gave a cry for Kord as I ran into the middle of the raging battle. And then I stopped.

There was no battle. There was barely any hint of a town. All around were decaying ruins. The most stable structure left was the temple of Kord. I thrust the doors open and cried with the horror of what had been done.

The walls were lined with the remains of my brethren, the brave followers of Kord that stayed behind to give us time to flee. Was my father amongst them, I wondered. The orcs had defiled and profaned this temple to Kord. It was overwhelming.

I ran out and got sick, cried, yelled with vengeance. I had always known that this was what we would find, but to find it, well, that was something harsh.

The others came down. They all looked away except Arry. He fixed me in the eye and asked me to stay with him to right the temple. The others flew off towards the darkness in the north. Arry and I are flying right now to catch up with them.

But once they had gone, Arry walked into the temple, said a few words, sprinkled some holy water, and the temple was cleaned and restored, filled with the divine wonder of Kord. It is like the great brawl room that is the great hall of Kord.

Arry motioned to me to come to the altar. There, at the head of it, was a stone tablet embedded in the floor with a sword lodged in it.

"Mord, do you know what this sword is? Can you read that tablet?"

"Of course, I can read it. I can read anything. Let me just reach out and, ow!" Electricity arced through me from the tablet, shocking me, but I defiantly held on, reading through the pain what was on the tablet.

HERE LIES THE GREATEST TRAITOR OF THEM ALL. ENTOMBED FOR ALL ETERNITY BEYOND THE REACH OF ALL.

It chilled me to think about that.

"Mord, I think this is where your father is. As he was a great orc chieftain before joining with us, he is probably the greatest traitor. I think they used powerful magic to seal him deep underground, a living torment for all eternity, denied the right to die, denied the right to be resurrected, denied the right to an after-life. It is a terrible fate."

"What can we do uncle?"

"Powerful magic can only be broken by even more powerful magic. And I feel that this is wizard magic. We need a wizard. That will take time. We will come back. But let's get the sword."

I grumbled, and then reached to take the sword. My hands grasped it and fire rinsed over me, burning me, scorching me. Arry kept healing me as I pulled on the sword. We were both nearly drained when finally the stone cracked and the sword flew up into the air and got stuck in the ceiling.

Arry shook his head, shot his hand out crying out, "Sword of Drok, come to me!" And the sword flew to him.

The sword of Drok? What was that?

"Come Mord. We have spent enough time here. We must go. I will tell you about this sword later."

Father, with the grace of Kord, I will find a way to release you.

Mords of Wisdom: The nightmare of a slaughter is not soon forgotten.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/ruins-of-a-home..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/ruins-of-a-home..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The End Begins]]></title><description><![CDATA[At last, at last. After much studying in that dratted elf's library, we are now done! Oh I hate reading. So boring.

But at last we get to see action. Uncle Arry and the council agree that we need to investigate the eastern continent and stop the demon plague. ISear seems very excited about this. He even gave Pitter a great cold-iron club. ISear will be traveling with us as will Arry. AllGrins is too busy with dwarf matters to go traveling with us anymore.

ISear argued that we should go straight to his mountain home, but Arry and me successfully argued that a slow approach would be good and so we shall go to the southern portion near the old Kord colony. To see that place fills me with excitement and anticipation. What will we find? What did happen to my father?

Tomorrow, tomorrow! I will find these answers. Me so awake!

Mords of Wisdom: To sleep, avoid anticipation.]]></description><link>http://mord.jostylr.com/the-end-begins..html</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://mord.jostylr.com/the-end-begins..html</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Mord Drom of Drok]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2014 13:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>